这是国际空间站上往下看的画面，好看吧
This is the view from the International Space Station, it’s pretty nice
对于在太空的宇航员来说这样的景色肯定老震撼了
For the astronauts living on the space station, a view like this may be awe-inspiring
但这也更加说明了往返地球是件多么危险的事情
but it also emphasises just how dangerous the return journey back to Earth really is
自从2011年航天飞机全部退役，俄罗斯的联盟号飞船成了去空间站的唯一船票
Since the Space Shuttle retired in 2011, the Russian “Soyuz” spacecraft has been the
only method of transporting humans to and from the ISS
2012年，太空叉使用他们的龙飞船成为了给国际空间站送货的第一家私人公司
In 2012, SpaceX became the first private company to send a cargo ship to the ISS using their Dragon Spacecraft
那么太空叉啥时候能送人去空间站呢？
But when are SpaceX going to send their first humans to the International Space Station?
这期咱来说说龙二飞船（以下简称龙二）
In this video we’re going to look at SpaceX’s Dragon 2 spacecraft
致力于送人去空间站以及更远地方的飞船
which aims to take humans to and from the International Space Station and beyond
我们还要讲讲太空叉造龙二时候要面对的问题
We’re also going to look at the problems SpaceX has had with Dragon 2
顺便提一下太空叉的对手波音
as well as taking a look at SpaceX’s close competition with Boeing
在太空叉早期的时候，他们的目标单纯的是造龙飞船给空间站往返送货
Early on in SpaceX’s history, the plan was to make a spacecraft called Dragon
which would be capable of delivering and returning cargo from the International Space Station
完成这个之后，他们就开始研究载人飞船了，也就是龙二
Once they achieved this, they would then focus on their human spacecraft, Dragon 2
设计可载7人安全往返地球与国际空间站
which was designed to carry a crew of 7 people to the ISS and return them safely back to Earth
龙二设计可安置在猎鹰九号和重型猎鹰上，可以与国际空间站对接
Dragon 2 was designed to launch on the Falcon 9 and Falcon Heavy rockets, dock with the ISS
可以返回地球，并使用安装在飞船一圈的八台SuperDraco发动机反推着陆
and then return to Earth with a propulsive landing using 8 SuperDraco engines
mounted around the perimeter of the spacecraft
使得龙二可以完全复用，还能执行受控着陆
This would allow the Dragon 2 spacecraft to be fully reusable as well as being able to perform controlled landings
2014年龙二亮相后，其经历了一系列测试
After its unveiling in 2014, Dragon 2 went through a number of tests
最开始是发射台终止测试，该测试在2015年5月成功完成
starting with a Pad Abort test which was successfully completed in May of 2015
这项测试展示了如果发射台出现紧急情况，龙二将怎样将宇航员安全带离至安全地点
The test showed how Dragon would carry astronauts to safety if an emergency occurred on the launch pad
当年晚些时候，太空叉还进行了龙二返回舱的悬停测试
Later that year, SpaceX also performed a propulsive hover test of the Dragon Capsule
从而演示它是如何控制反推着陆的
to demonstrate how the vehicle could be controlled during a propulsive landing
至今，龙二已经经历一系列改变
Since then, the Dragon 2 Spacecraft has gone through a number of changes
相比最初计划已经鸽两年了
delaying it’s initial launch by over 2 years
太空叉后来取消了反推着陆，因为让NASA相信这玩意安全可靠的话浪费时间又浪费钱
SpaceX decided to scrap the propulsive landing idea since it would take a lot of time and money
to prove to NASA that it was safe for crewed flights
他们还感觉在龙二上拖太久，花太多钱，也会严重拖慢BFR的进度
They also realized that spending more time and money on the Dragon spacecraft
would take away from the progress being made on the BFR
而且龙二能做的，BFR也能做到，做的还更好
which will be able to do everything that Dragon is capable of, and much more
因此，龙二直接改回大家最熟悉的着陆技术：伞降、海上溅落
Instead, the spacecraft will have a more familiar landing technique: deploying parachutes
and splashing down in the ocean
那么现在太空叉也知道龙二咋回事了，问题是它啥时候能上天呢？
Now that SpaceX has a clearer understanding of how Dragon 2 will work, the question is when will it launch?
啥时候能看太空叉执行载人航天任务呢？
And when will we eventually see humans launch onboard a SpaceX rocket?
龙二的第一个任务暂定今年八月
The very first mission for the Dragon 2 capsule is scheduled to launch later this year in August
不载人，只是向NASA演示龙二可以和空间站对接，并返回地球
This mission will be an uncrewed test flight to demonstrate to NASA that the vehicle is
capable of docking with the ISS and returning safely to Earth
如果任务成功，太空叉定于今年12月送人去国际空间站
If this first mission is a success, SpaceX will then attempt to launch a Dragon capsule
with humans onboard to the ISS in December of this year
但无论这两件事结果如何，太空叉还必须进行一次飞行中中止测试
But before either of those two missions can go ahead, SpaceX will have to perform an in-flight abort test
时间定于今年晚些时候，在刚提到的两次任务之间
which is scheduled to take place later this year between the two demo flights
测试中飞船将在最大动压的时候使用SuperDraco发动机把龙二拽离火箭
This test will use the SuperDraco engines to pull the Dragon capsule away from the rocket as it goes through Max Q
在看谁能先送美国人去国际空间站的比赛里，太空叉有个对手
In the race to launch American astronauts to the ISS, SpaceX has some competition
波音的CST-100天际线飞船载人飞行的暂定日期比太空叉早一个月——今年11月
Boeing are looking to launch their Crew Capsule, the CST-100 Starliner
a month earlier than SpaceX in November
两家公司和NASA都签了合同，每年至少送一次人去国际空间站
Both companies have already been awarded contracts by NASA to perform at least 1 mission to the ISS each year
当两家公司都成功的时候，太空叉那边会便宜一点
When both companies eventually get their Spacecrafts off the ground, SpaceX will be the cheaper option for NASA
但是既然一年只射两次
However, since they will only be doing around 2 flights per year
龙二也用不着频繁复用
the Dragon spacecraft doesn’t need to be rapidly reusable
这也是为啥他们放弃了反推着陆
which is another reason they gave up on the propulsive landing idea
所以当我们等太空叉搞载人航天等得望眼欲穿的时候
So while we eagerly wait for SpaceX to launch their first humans into space
别忘了他们为了让那玩意上天还是付出了很多努力滴
we can appreciate how much work goes into making the spacecrafts that will take them there
另外尽管离龙二真正能干大事还早
And although Dragon 2 has taken a while to come to fruition
但太空叉离载人航天这个成就越来越近，我们有目共睹
it does seem like we're finally on our way to seeing SpaceX launch their first humans into space
这可是去火星路途上一个里程碑呀！
An important milestone in the overall journey to Mars
所以你们觉得龙二咋样呢？
What do you think of the dragon 2 spacecraft?
今年能射吗？会咕咕咕到明年吗？
Will it launch this year or will we have to wait even longer to see it’s maiden voyage?
喜欢给虫的话 也可以给给虫充电呀
喜欢这个视频的话，欢迎成为这个YouTuber——Primal Space的赞助者
If you enjoyed this video and would like to become one of our first contributors to Primal Space
充电按钮就在右边
地址在Patreon.com/PrimalSpace
please visit Patreon.com/PrimalSpace
也别忘了关注、点赞、分享、收藏、投币一波哦
and make sure you’re subscribed so you can join the discussion as we continue to learn more about all things space
最后感谢观看，字幕翻译给虫，下个视频见
Thank you very much for watching and I’ll see you in the next video